Okay!
What was that?
That's enough out of you, okay
It's weird. I tried to
start streaming
but it said it didn't connect and then
I've never seen that message before. First time
Hello Kombayn Nikoladze. You're on Windows 11, I believe.
Has it really been a minute already?
Okay.
Let's go
Let's go back to the city.
Windows 12 is coming soon?
Uh... I'll try not to get it.
My same growing pain when I switched from
10 to 11 a bunch of software stopped working
but it's back to normal now kinda
Where am I going?
I'm going to shop.
I want to buy some tools.
Can I buy a sword?
Cynth, you got a sword?
Ooh I can buy
Look how expensive!
Don't be a stranger!
You're welcome. Don't be
Get equipment tempered.
Good to go!
Don't rush me!
Kom kom putt pu
Now which of the
Cuz its defense
Percentage-based, which
So it's probably just plus one?
Yeah it's one, okay, thanks.
Is this truly the best use of my raval
Hello Croez.
All right, well.
I still don't b
From the fur of m
I've received zero.
Storehouse
Whooh! Ha ha ha!
I'm wet! I'm getting wetter!
Will I know a raval ore drop if I see one?
No!
No! I got wetted
I'm always wet!
Hello verily save the adverb.
Throw shade at Dougherty?
Ooh, I leveled up.
There's nothing else in here
Throw shade at Dougherty. I'd rather throw
No!
I forgot I had a double jump.
It's your classic double-jump.
I'm getting wet!
Are we suppo
I feel like I
Oh my gosh!
This enemy
Robal. Robal~ !
Is this where I wanted to go?
Surprised that that didn't hit me.
I'm full on hit points...
Oh dear. Something big
Oh! I got clubbed!
Ow... I uh
I killed somethin
A powered up Radel
Strikes the ground
Ok, Do-radel.
No longer singing hello it's me.
Put on the fireworks.
No!
Throw Doughe
Raval ore times twenty-five!
Don't walk into the attack!
Look who it is.
Unfortunately, he cannot jump and cannot climb s
Very unfortunate for Do-Radel
Can I jump in? No I can't jump in this.
Nothing back here.
I hear something funky. No!
What did I just kill?
Barlen. Upgraden Barl
A lfying jell
Shares basic structrue
Fozen! Oh, it's the mitotic slime. Of course. Fozen...
Oh gosh...
Noice troy!
Ohhhhh...
Oh my gosh. Look here.
I'm getting owned. Alll right
Gel-Grad. My mic volume is low. Is it?
Okay...
How about this? :-)
I call myself lowering it a little bit but..
More?
This feels too quiet to me.
Take that!
There's like rocks up there, bu
Just low ceillings.
Oops! Ohhhhhhh
THWACK! THWACK! THWACK!
I am so dead lol.
I am... so dead. Okay.
We did...
not equip okay good job.
I can't hear the music.
I messed up the volume balance again
I should have teleported
I'm getting wet!
Just planningon how I'm gonna get ovr
I gotta press like three buttons on the controll
I gotta do an up
then pull out my vicious tornado.
Can't hide from me.
Fozen
Healing.
Also, how's the volume now?
There was no effect!
Noooo.
Vicious winds. Winds of fury!
Okay, nothing there.
What?!
We can not get there from here.
Okay how would I get there?
Oh, it's there.
I can't see!
Don't be rushing me like this. Ow...
There's so many enem
There's trink
Okay, let's try to make our way back up there so I can try to make that... one jump.
That wasn't it.
Oh I forgot I had a double jump. Wait, this
All right.
Actually, I think I've been here before.
This was where I got like fifty Raa
Yeah, see I've already been here.
So I do need to go dow
Where I was.
I mean...
It was very obviously progress
Oh gosh.
What?
I still got hit.
Well executed.
THWACK!
Take that, you scumbag.
Duradel... Duradel diddle dum diddle do.
I'm expecting to find something behind the stairwell.
What?
Learned my insults from 90's kid movies hahaha
Raval ore times twenty-five again
Is that what that insult's from?
THWACK!
That's so messed up. It hits me on the way down.
This thing is here...
Take that!
Take that, scumbag.
It's like another owl again. The owls are always here.
Come here.
You coward lol
It's probably best if I find a save point first or something down here.
Get out of my face!
Hello?
Seven nice hits and that enemy is dead.
Okay, there's a stairwell down there.
Thought there was a stairwell over here but there's not.
MISS!
Uhh... all right
THWACK! THWACK! THWACK!
You stairwell camping hoochee!
Oh, look who's here.
Oh, there's something up there.
Pot of money.
4906. I can see my gold on this screen and my raval ore.
Was that a mozgouz?
I figured it would go off on the stairs but it DIDN'T!
Bring your butt back here and get these whippings.
Get these whippin's
Where did I fall from? I feel like there's something over there because there's no guardrail
Yeah, this is... I've been here already.
Take a big jump
Oh, we made it.
What do we find? Not a save point. We found more enemies.
THWACK! THWACK! THWACK!
Nooo~ Don't do that!
Oh my gosh. You massive cheater!
Okay I guess you were supposed to fall off these jumps here and have to deal with those.
Is this progress? This feels like progress.
Oh my gosh.
THWACK! THWACK! THWACK! NO! Oh my gosh...
Get out of my face
It's like the enemy places the hammer onto the ground then I fall onto the hammer and get k
Okay, what is this platforming here?
All right, come on up here
THWACK! THWACK! THWACK!
THWACK!
Take that, you scumbag.
Warming up to you though
Oh dear. I don't have my step now
Shucks, that didn't work.
Oh the step is over there.
Owned lol
Da- doggone it!
I didn't want you to go that far.
Okay, are we done yet.
I've found a skeletal warrior?
Can I kill you through the wall? I guess eventually.
One damage eventually will kill them even
I need my bomb power there
Oh, there's light
Oh yes!
Yessssss
These controls.
Aban Mine
Now the question: do I
I do want to go back to that one r
Maybe we'll spend like 30 minute
They're not even there anymore. Oh there they are.
POOMP!
You think these enemies oneshot me?
They're also massive cheaters. Look how far they're into the
I'm out of magic.
All right, there are more productive things to do with our time.
I can only do like single hits.
No! Why would you do that?
All right.
Ooh I foun
Raval ore times sixty-five. Okay!
THWACK! THWACK!
Okay, we also need to explore what's in th
Oh, I am... alive.
Thwack thwack thwack...
All right, settle down.
A chest over there.
I'll never be able to climb stairs.
Thwack... ooh, he's thwacking his way up the stairs.
Oh my gosh I don't want to go th
Up the stairs.
Got him.
Raval ore times fourty.
Okay, maybe this is just a pit of Duradels.
Okay that was a very forgiving jump there. Katol Elixir!
What is this? A ceramic pendant mirac
We got a miss
I never used this.
I never used these.
I can afford to go back and upgrade my stuff.
I do want to go to that one chest and then we'll u
We'll go back and upgrade our equipment.
Um okay I'm down here.
Actually I think the way up is back this way.
Yeah remember that stair camping hoochee.
Okay is it up this way?
Yeah here we go
So I wanna double-jump.
Like an ANGEL!?
Do not thwack me of
Oh gosh
There's multiple of them
Emerald!
Thanks, chest.
You've got a nice levelup. Okay
So we got two emeralds and we got t
This sounds like a great time to go back and upgrade our equipment.
Don't be a stranger. Can I buy this? Of course not.
Don't be a stranger.
Okay, I guess we can just upgrade all of these. It's like four defense.
You can also upgrade
Okay, the blacksmith is rippe
Who keeps rushin
I'm too busy sitting over here looking busy.
Okay... Aban mine.
Whooh!
THWACK!
Oh gosh, here we go
The fundam
How absurd the ice is in this game. THWACK!
Like you're one ice, you have nothing but
You can't like stop, you can't like change directions very easily.
THWACK!
All right, danmaku boss I believe. Noooo!
No!
Oh gosh...
Mm-mm, mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Doggone it, all right.
This ice, man!
Okay.
Hello!
NOPE!
Okay.
I don't know why I'm standing so far away from this boss. Didn't I die last time because I was standing too far away?
Nice, okay. I won.
uwu my items better.
Darkness Statue! Behold the statue
Whooh! Okay.
You can't go in there. Let me guess. Chester is just outside.
Depths. I wanna go to the storehouse.
Right, they're not here anymore. They wisely decided to leave. Okay I guess I'm going to the city.
Gardner's gone.
It looks like we've got a lot more monsters on our hands.
They're all over Felghana
Things could get rough with
By the way, you have
I noticed some Raval Ore missing from th
She's crafting me the Ultima Weapon, obviously.
Wipe out all the monsters so I can eat yummy food again.
Just keep on moving.
Bob.
Nightfire Gem.
Mm-hmm...
Wait hold on.
Emits a bright light.
You know what we're about to do.
Oh my gosh I an
Wait this room was already lit up
Game changer!
Let's explore this place again.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, she's not here.
Are these games that I played as a kid?
Hey mommy I hid your car keys. Can you find them for me?
This voice actor also sounds familiar.
Hello Etanks.
I need a hero. I'm holding out for a hero til
Raval ore times ten in the pikkard coop.
Is there one back there? Okay, so we're hunting for medic
And... car keys.
A shoe that gives you perfect friction on even the slipp
You know how much I would love shoes that don't slip and slide and subject me to the worst ice in the 21st century and we're not even halfway tho
I don't know. I've found zero f
I don't think there are any here.
Maybe they're inside these houses.
Lochus.
It's cussed.
Cussed.
The king said a bad word.
Hope I'm pressing the right button to search. What if it's a different button?
Unmarked in the cold
You got any booty in here, grandma?
Can we go into the well and get the lens of truth?
I guess not.
Don't be a stranger.
This stuff is so expensiiiiiive.
I was just checking in for an appointment to get my spear all sharpened up.
Okay.
What'd you call me?
I'm ruing. Anyone ruing?
I'm ruing.
I'm so screwed!
"Red". No, it's a lot of trinkets and jewelries that are missing.
Where's Elena?
I can't find the booty!
It's not in the inn!
Maybe the booty's in the church. You know what?
Ten hunks of it for 500 Gold? 500?!
Oh my gosh that was so not worth it. Oh he wants more. Fifty hunks.
Hunks...
I buried them all across this LAND-lubbin' town. Okay,
Two of me treasure be baking in the sun
Thar be no X markin these spots.
All right.
Chapel booty.
Oh..
Is it just this?
It's also clearly marked. Clearly... the
Wait.
All right fine, you know what we'
I can just dou
I can't double-jump in
Oh my gosh, it's t
It's those darn edicts and those tax
I have to interact with this. No wonder I could
All right. Church booty. Wait.
What is this glitchy area here. What in the world? Wait...
Can't double jump in the church o
Oh my gosh, it's so easy.
Tree booty.
Making sure it's not in her bed.
Okay so the last one is indoors.
So we found the one in the nest. I found progress.
You rescued Lezard Valeth. No one told me.
Galbalan!
Mmmm... I think I'll be fine. Oops, that's not the tal
All right, you got
Got some booty in your drawers?
That's a flower.
Any booty in here?
Y'all seen any booty? That booty booty?
Any booty back here?
Hmm... where could that booty be?
Any booty in here. Booty inspector.
FBI. Felghana Booty Inspector. That's me.
Okay, I'm running out of houses to look in.
Okay uh let's go to the mountains.
Actually mmmmmmm there are a few places I want to go.
I've got double jump.
Illburns drop-off? Topside, I believe.
Yeah, here we go.
Ominous camera zoom-in on this cave.
Katol Elixir!
Oh I came all this way for an Elixir.
Max HP up!
All right um...
I can't think of anything else I needed a double-jump for. Whoops.
Uhhh...
Let's go to the Elderm Mountains.
I can't belli
Pokemon evolution.
Double-jump your way up to the mountains.
Squawk! Why does that
Kradel? Subspec
All right, Kradel. Kradel to the grave. Nothing over there.
Okay, what are you? Halick. A burrower
You can see its tail protruding from the soil. Can I?
Oh my gosh.
Miss!
Wait, did I miss? I feel like I attacked the ground and it walked into the at
Look how much blood. Insect!
Jigel. Jy gell. Mud wasp. A mud wasp?!
What is a mud wasp? Is that like a...
Squawk.
See a rock ceiling over here.
I was thinking it would be like a Picmole but no. Just a mud wasp.
Take that!
Mmmm...
Okay you gotta look carefully for those tails.
Raval ore times ninety.
Oh my gosh.
Okay so that was the ceiling I saw earlier.
Have I monitored my windows processes lately? No...
Have I defragmented my disk?
All right, come here.
All right, get
What? How dare you not get stunned?!
All right, we're in.
Take that, you scumbag. What was that?
That ice looked like recoil. Recoil ice.
Need the icebreaker.
All right, can't jump down from here. Only up.
Oh my gosh, these bees!
No, don't get stung. I'm allergic.
Well, I can't say no to this, can I. Oh, it's just some money. Just some money.
13000. Very close to be able to afford some of that high-end gear from Cynthia's shop.
I feel like at some point, there are going to be spikes here and I need to avoid these. You know what?
Squawk.
It's like progress.
Get out of here, bee.
Berm Leaves, okay.
Oops, wrong button.
You may be surprised that I'm still pressing wrong buttons 4 hours into my playthrough.
Okay, I just passed up another road that probably is not progress now.
So naturally, I'm continuing. Oh this one goes outside. I don't know about this way.
All right, let's go back and look for the Ice Sword. Oh hello, what's up here?
Raval ore times seventy.
I killed it.
Zolmie, okay. Gotta
Ilba? Idris Ilba (shell)?
A large lump of rock.
Okay, well.
My magic wasn't doing much against it either but we made do.
Watch this also be progress. No, calm down. It surfaces without w
Oh dear. Raval ore times fifty.
Back to more of this.
I'm... I can't press the pause button because it's not the start button
Why does the start button do this? It does the same thing as this button, which is the L Button?
I don't even think that was a prize anyway. Looks like a death trap.
Hey, wait your turn! Okay.
Squawk.
Excuse me. That is not copacetic.
Come back here! Oh my gosh.
I feel like I'm supposed to be hunting this mountain to find these things.
Raval ore times ninety.
I've got nothing to use it on... yet!
Once I buy this uh... Banded gear, we'll have something to use it on.
NO.
Squawk squawk.
What are you doing? Bouncing up and down.
Oh my gosh. Ice sword please.
Without warning!
Oh gosh. Just say no.
LOL you can't even open a chest without bouncing around.
Obnoxiously having to press the
Why are you down here?! Go away!
Can I get some healing please?
Ice Physics. Ice Physcis are bae. This game has the strongest Ice Physics in any game that I've ever played.
Like imagine Mega Man if you couldn't jump to reset your ice physics.
I didn't actually explore that room all the way.
I was kinda hoping to get a health drop. Good grief, we're still at 71 HP.
Okay, there we go. We got something.
Is that a Samurai Kitty? Samurai Pizz
Pashhow. A per
Looks like a cat but thinks it's
It's a samurai cat.
It might be nice to have 69 HP but I don't think so.
Let's just go back.
The aliens will ask for our equations. Oops. Do
16000. I only need 1400 more and I can get a Banded Shield.
A Banded Slayer.
Hatchet-like weapon pieced together by a madman.
Get a Katol Elixir. A holy spring in the Elderm Mounta
We should be able to find a bunch here.
Base. Base, we have an intruder.
I'll robably go for like 20 more minutes.
That's not the jump button.
Are you flying in the ground? Get y
You silly mud wasp.
Oh gosh.
I need that money. Papa wants a Banded Armor.
I stunned the bee. It's a mud wasp. Stop calling it a bee.
Entomologists watching right now are furious.
Not a very graceful victory there.
Oh, it's gone.
Yes, I got it!
Ilba. Large lump of rock.
Not the jump button!
You saw that jump? What in the world? Oops!
Raval ore times seventy.
Bye. Good bye!
Wrong move for you there, buddy.
Oh gosh.
There we go!
You need to get stunned when I do the attack which
That chest...
How do I get there?
How do I get THERE?
I'm just gonna assume that I jump down from some
There's nothing over there, though.
Maybe it's back here...
How do I get there?
Maybe I gotta like caress the wall
Nowhere to get over there.
Gotta caress the walls while jump as well.
Oh my gosh.
Raval ore times fourty.
Money is getting up there.
How do I get there?
Hmm... hmm indeed.
You can't get there from here. Nor from there.
How would you get there?
Save point. Yos!
Me too!
When are you gonna stop sending henchmen after me an
The furries. No!
Ye ah oo oo ya !
NO!
Okay, they're both immune to this.
They're like the scouters from Chrono Trigger. They only go
Blue is sword magic lol okay.
Exclamation boost I don't have exclamation boost power.
LMAO LMAO!
Exclamation.... wait no no exclamation
Exclamation BOOST! Oh my gosh.
What are these hadoukens?
Oh my gosh I fell on a musical note and died.
Let's take out red, maybe.
MISS! Oh my gosh.
All right.
FIRE!
Get out of the way. Oh my gosh.
oo e ah oe oeeo ee oee ah! You know what would help? Dodging.
Oh my gosh.
oo ee aa ee oaa o aaaaaaah! All right, come here, Blue.
Harpy: "Wow, he went down quick"... lol "Quick". Didn't one of y'all die?
I could have taken him out in my sleep.
Exclamation boost!
THWACK!
I'm ready to fall on a musical note and DIE! I
I didn't fall on a musical no
All right, excuse me. Beep beep.
Exclamation boost! Oh... she's already
Wow, she went down quick!
Oh my gosh.
O o o e e oe eo ee oeo oeo oe
Oh no.
O o e e o e oh
Oh my gosh.
All right...
One more, one more!
One more and we'll try again. I gotta take off.
THWACK!
Exclamation boost! I missed the button!
All right, exclamation boost.
All right, never mind. Bail.
All right.
All right, I won.
Weren't you watching?
Mmm... floaters better grab a life vest.
Okay, we did it, and I gotta cut stream. Thanks for watching!
Okay, good bye!